<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Amazing Sid</title><link>http://example.org/</link><description>About uBlogger Theme</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 11:31:03 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The mean crab and the smart snail</title><link>http://example.org/posts/snail-and-carb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 11:31:03 +1000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>http://example.org/posts/snail-and-carb/</guid><description><![CDATA[It was a nice weather at the county side. The sun was bright and the air was cool and light.
The snail came out of his shell for a walk. While he was slithering through the big beach rocks, he went across crab&rsquo;s house. Crab poked his long thin eyes out of the pitch black hole. &ldquo;Hello crab&rdquo;, said snail moving one inch closer to crab&rsquo;s house, leaving a silvery trial.]]></description></item><item><title>mystery of the secret lab</title><link>http://example.org/posts/mystorylab/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 11:31:03 +1000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>http://example.org/posts/mystorylab/</guid><description><![CDATA[It was windy at Black Hills. The moon rose up high in the cloudless sky. Sid was up doing research for his boss Metros.
Right then the telephone rang, it was a call from the Black Hills&rsquo;s counsel. &ldquo;Hello, who is this&rdquo;, Sid asked answering the telephone. &ldquo;Steve from the counsil of Black Hills&rdquo; answered from the otherside of the tellephone. &ldquo;Sid, you have a mission to keep your eye on, There is another spy who calls himself &ldquo;Jack&rdquo; has decided to put poison in the whole town and we will have do anything that he says after he drops it&rdquo;, Steve said with fear in his voice.]]></description></item><item><title>Inventions</title><link>http://example.org/posts/invensions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 19:21:03 +1000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>http://example.org/posts/invensions/</guid><description>INVENTIONSBENJAMIN FANKLINBenjamin Franklin was born on January 17th 1706 in Boston, Massachusetts. He first became known to the public as the publisher of the newspaper, The Pennsylvania Gazette. Did you know that Benjamin Franklin was one of the five members that drafted the declaration of independence? Perhaps he is most famous for work with electricity. His experiments helped prove that lightning is a form of electricity. Franklin invented the lighting rod which helped buildings to keep safe from lightning.</description></item></channel></rss>