<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts - Amazing Sid</title><link>http://example.org/posts/</link><description>All Posts | Amazing Sid</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 19:21:03 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Inventions</title><link>http://example.org/posts/invensions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 19:21:03 +1000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>http://example.org/posts/invensions/</guid><description>INVENTIONSBENJAMIN FANKLINBenjamin Franklin was born on January 17th 1706 in Boston, Massachusetts. He first became known to the public as the publisher of the newspaper, The Pennsylvania Gazette. Did you know that Benjamin Franklin was one of the five members that drafted the declaration of independence? Perhaps he is most famous for work with electricity. His experiments helped prove that lightning is a form of electricity. Franklin invented the lighting rod which helped buildings to keep safe from lightning.</description></item><item><title>mystery of the secret lab</title><link>http://example.org/posts/mystorylab/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 11:31:03 +1000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>http://example.org/posts/mystorylab/</guid><description><![CDATA[​	It was windy at Black Hills. The moon rose up high in the cloudless sky. Sid was up doing research for his boss called Metros. Right then a call from the Black Hills&rsquo;s counsel called on the telephone. &ldquo;Hello Steve&rdquo;, Sid said putting the telephone on his ear. Steve was the counsel of Black Hills. &ldquo;Sid the spy you have a mission to keep in your eye . There is another spy that called Jack has decided to put a poison on the hole town and we will do anything that he says after he drops it&rdquo;, Steve said with fear in his voice.]]></description></item></channel></rss>